Oh, that is so, so...
I'm sorry, I gotta run. If you
come up with an adjective, text me.
[DOOR CLOSES]
(Sheldon:)Inconsiderate. That is the adjective.
Inconsiderate.
(Leonard(exiting the apartment):)You can stare at your board all day,
she's still going to be right.
SHELDON:
I'm not staring, I'm mulling.
- Oh, hey, Leonard.
- Hi.
[TEASING]
So how's it going?
[IMITATES PENNY]
Pretty good.
Just pretty good? I'd think
you were doing very good.
"Pretty, very." There's really no objective
scale for delineating variations of good.
(Leonard:)Why do you ask?
(Penny:)Well, a little bird told me that
you and Leslie hooked up last night.
- Sheldon!
SHELDON: I'm coming.
So is it serious? Do you like her?